Guide to the Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of Art public relations and graphics records circa 1942-2009 COR0003.3.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Graphics, Circa 1990 - 2006; Series 12
  - The Quilt's of Gee's Bend, 2004; Series 12 (Box 136, Folder 8)
  - Robert Lewis Folk to Folk, 2004; Series 12 (Box 136, Folder 9)
  - [Loose Graphic Documents], Circa 2005; Series 12 (Box 138, Folder 1)
  - Inventions Recent Painting by Cato Fonseca, 2005; Series 12 (Box 138, Folder 2)
  - Closer to Home: The 48th Corcoran Biennial, 2005; Series 12 (Box 138, Folder 3)
  - Closer to Home: The 48th Corcoran Biennial, 2005; Series 12 (Box 138, Folder 4)
  - Slides for Corcoran Publications, Circa 1990-1999; Series 12 (Box 153, Folder 1)
  - Graphic Design II-IV, Circa 1990-1999; Series 12 (Box 153, Folder 2)
  - Graphic Design, Circa 1990-1999; Series 12 (Box 153, Folder 3)
  - DC Out-Takes, Circa 1990-1999; Series 12 (Box 153, Folder 4)
  - Print-Making / Ceramics / 3-D Sculpture, Circa 1990-1999; Series 12 (Box 153, Folder 5)
  - Graphic Design - 3-D Projects and Posters, Circa 1990-1999; Series 12 (Box 153, Folder 6)
  - Foundation Resources, Circa 1990-1999; Series 12 (Box 153, Folder 7)
  - Foundation Resources, Circa 1990-1999; Series 12 (Box 153, Folder 8)
- Suzan Reed Weaver publication files, 1973-2006; Series 14
  This series is arranged in two subseries: Corcoran publications and Freelance publications.
  Biographical
  Suzan Reed Weaver worked at the Corcoran as Graphic Art Director from 1980-1996, and worked for the Corcoran in a freelance capacity from 1978-1980 and after 1996 into the 2000s, until her death in 2017. Reed Weaver defined and installed the Corcoran's in-house graphics department, established graphics guidelines and standards for the Corcoran Gallery and School, and managed exhibition and publications graphics. Through her studio, Suzan Reed Graphics, Suzan Reed Weaver completed additional freelance projects for The Corcoran Gallery of Art and affiliated organizations, as well as additional institutions and organizations.
  This series contains publications and professional files from former Corcoran employee Suzan Reed Weaver. Material includes Corcoran publications and publications from outside organizations related to Suzan Reed Weaver's freelance work.
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  Transferred to George Washington University by Geoff Reed (Suzan Reed Weaver's brother and executor of her estate) in August 2017.
  - Corcoran publications, 1973-2002; Series 14 Subseries 1
    The materials are arranged alphabetically by publication type.
    This subseries contains Corcoran publications and files, including annual reports, budget reports, exhibition catalogs, invitations, mailings, and newsletters.
    - The 1869 Society, 1992-1995; Series 14 Subseries 1 (Box 165, Folder 1)
    - Annual Report, 1974-1983; Series 14 Subseries 1 (Box 165, Folder 2)
    - Benefit Invitations, 1991-1995; Series 14 Subseries 1 (Box 165, Folder 3)
    - Columns, 1995, 2001-2002; Series 14 Subseries 1 (Box 165, Folder 4)
    - Corcoran Ball, 1988-1996; Series 14 Subseries 1 (Box 165, Folder 5)
    - Corcoran Cafe, Undated; Series 14 Subseries 1 (Box 165, Folder 6)
    - Education Programs, 1980-1996; Series 14 Subseries 1 (Box 165, Folder 7)
    - Envelopes, Undated; Series 14 Subseries 1 (Box 165, Folder 8)
    - Event Invitations, 1990-1999; Series 14 Subseries 1 (Box 165, Folder 9)
    - Exhibition Opening Invitations, 1994-1997; Series 14 Subseries 1 (Box 165, Folder 10)
    - Exhibition Publications, 1980-1996; Series 14 Subseries 1 (Box 165, Folders 11-12)
    - Financial - Budgets, 1990-1997; Series 14 Subseries 1 (Box 165, Folder 13)
    - Fundraising Flyers - Annual Fund, 1994-1996; Series 14 Subseries 1 (Box 165, Folder 14)
    - Fundraising Flyers - Business, 1994-1996; Series 14 Subseries 1 (Box 165, Folder 15)
    - Fundraising Flyers - Membership, 1987-1998; Series 14 Subseries 1 (Box 165, Folder 16)
    - Gallery One, 1989-1996; Series 14 Subseries 1 (Box 165, Folder 17)
    - Hospice: A Photographic Inquiry, 1995-1996; Series 14 Subseries 1 (Box 165, Folder 18)
    - Museum Flyers, Undated; Series 14 Subseries 1 (Box 165, Folder 19)
    - Music Events, 1986-1992; Series 14 Subseries 1 (Box 165, Folder 20)
    - Newsletter/Calendar, 1983-1985; Series 14 Subseries 1 (Box 165, Folder 21)
    - Newsletter/Calendar, 1986-1987; Series 14 Subseries 1 (Box 165, Folder 22)
    - Newsletter/Calendar, 1988-1989; Series 14 Subseries 1 (Box 165, Folder 23)
    - Newsletter/Calendar, 1990-1991; Series 14 Subseries 1 (Box 165, Folder 24)
    - Newsletter/Calendar, 1992-1993; Series 14 Subseries 1 (Box 165, Folder 25)
    - Newsletter/Calendar, 1994; Series 14 Subseries 1 (Box 166, Folder 1)
    - Night and Day, 1994-1997; Series 14 Subseries 1 (Box 166, Folder 2)
    - Photos, Undated; Series 14 Subseries 1 (Box 166, Folder 3)
    - Policy Statement - Freedom of Expression, Undated; Series 14 Subseries 1 (Box 166, Folder 4)
    - Postcards/Letters, Undated; Series 14 Subseries 1 (Box 166, Folder 5)
    - Program Flyers, 1985-1995; Series 14 Subseries 1 (Box 166, Folder 6)
    - School Publications, 1973-1997; Series 14 Subseries 1 (Box 166, Folder 7)
    - Shop Publications, Undated; Series 14 Subseries 1 (Box 166, Folder 8)
    - Spectrum Exhibition, 1986; Series 14 Subseries 1 (Box 166, Folder 9)
    - Student Events, 1982-1996; Series 14 Subseries 1 (Box 167, Folder 1)
    - The Sun King Exhibition, 1984-1985; Series 14 Subseries 1 (Box 167, Folder 2)
  - Freelance publications, 1989-2006; Series 14 Subseries 2
    The materials are arranged alphabetically by organization or institution.
    This subseries contains files, mailings, and publications related to Suzan Reed Weaver's professional activities outside of the Corcoran.
    - Arthritis Foundation, 2003-2005; Series 14 Subseries 2 (Box 167, Folder 3)
    - The Choral Arts Society of Washington, 2002-2006; Series 14 Subseries 2 (Box 167, Folder 4)
    - Discovery Creek, 2004-2006; Series 14 Subseries 2 (Box 167, Folder 5)
    - District of Columbia Jewish Community Center, 1998; Series 14 Subseries 2 (Box 167, Folder 6)
    - Flyers, 1989-2005; Series 14 Subseries 2 (Box 167, Folder 7)
    - Government, 1997; Series 14 Subseries 2 (Box 167, Folder 8)
    - Invitations, 1996; Series 14 Subseries 2 (Box 167, Folder 9)
    - King Hussein Foundation International, Undated; Series 14 Subseries 2 (Box 167, Folder 10)
    - Meridian International Center, 2004; Series 14 Subseries 2 (Box 167, Folder 11)
    - National Geographic, 1991; Series 14 Subseries 2 (Box 167, Folder 12)
    - Personal Papers, Undated; Series 14 Subseries 2 (Box 167, Folder 13)
    - Smithsonian Institution, 2004; Series 14 Subseries 2 (Box 167, Folder 14)